JORGE MUNOZ



📞 (206)-586-3307 | 🖂 munozmjorgel@gmail.com | 🔘 github.com/Jorgeluismunoz

SUMMARY

I currently enrolled an AAS Computer and Software Development. I have a great capacity for selflearning, experience with teamwork, empathy for problem solving and a high sense of commitment and responsibility so I can guarantee that the task assigned to me will be handled diligently. However, when difficulties occasionally arise that may hinder the development of the activity, I propose useful solutions and alternatives to speed up response times.

SKILLS

- Skilled at analyzing and solving problems.
- Able to work with different O.S; Windows, macOS and Linux.
- Basic knowledge in programming languages: Java, C#, PHP, SQL, HTML, JavaScript.
- Proficient in graphic design; Photoshop, Flash, Illustrator.

- knowledge with Android studio.
- Able to work as part of a team.
- Ability to work under pressure.
- Received award monthly better performance and quality of service.
- Speak Spanish (Native), English (Medium), Portuguese (Medium).

EXPERIENCE

02/2017 to 10/2017 Monitoring Analyst

Dayco Host - Venezuela, Caracas.

Monitor the company's network in order to maintain an optimal service and 100% operability. Perform preventive and corrective maintenance of physical and virtual equipment. If there is an anomaly in the network, solve it immediately or escalate it to the group in charge.

02/2016 to 01/2017 Project Engineer

Neuronet Technology – Venezuela, Caracas.

In charge of coordinating the installation and commissioning of telecommunication projects such as radio link installation, service extensions, network service migrations, etc. Remotely organize groups responsible for the execution of the project.

02/2015 to 12/2015 Professor

UMC - Venezuela, Vargas.

Professor of Electrical Networks I for Maritime Engineers in the Maritime University.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

02/2008 to 07/2013 Bachelor of Science: Telecommunication

UNEFA - Venezuela, Sucre.

12/2018 - Current Associate of Applied Science: Software Development

LwTech - Kirkland, WA.